The true story of a larger than life friendship
Zoo is a family, war, history film directed by Colin McIvor.
Young Tom and his misfit friends fight to save 'Buster' the baby elephant
during the German air raid bombings of Belfast in 1941.
Tom Hall, played by Art Parkinson.
Jane Berry, played by Emily Flain.
Security Guard Charlie, played by Toby Jones.
Pete, played by Ian O'Reilly.
Mr. Shawcross, played by Ian McElhinney.
Denise Austin, played by Penelope Wilton.
Zoo is a 2017 historical war family drama film
directed and written by Colin McIvor.
The film, based on a true story, stars Dame Penelope Wilton, Art Parkinson, Toby
Jones, Ian O'Reilly, Ian McElhinney, Amy Huberman, and Damian O'Hare.
As the Belfast Blitz ravages the city, a lonely widow, and an awkward teenager with friends take an
elephant named Buster from the city zoo, and hide it in the widow's terraced house back yard.
The film explores themes of elephant, world war ii, zoo,
based on true story, northern ireland.